The most terrifying ride you'll ever take
The Midnight Meat Train is a horror, mystery,
fantasy film directed by Ryuhei Kitamura.
A photographer's obsessive pursuit of dark subject matter leads him into the path of a serial killer
who stalks late night commuters, ultimately butchering them in the most gruesome ways.
Leon Kaufman, played by Bradley Cooper.
Mahogany, played by Vinnie Jones.
Susan Hoff, played by Brooke Shields.
Maya, played by Leslie Bibb.
Jurgis, played by Roger Bart.
Randle Cooper, played by Ted Raimi.
The Midnight Meat Train is a 2008 American horror film based on
Clive Barker's 1984 short story of the same name.
Its plot follows a photographer who attempts to track down a serial killer dubbed the "Subway
Butcher", and discovers more than he bargained for under the city streets.
Directed by Ryuhei Kitamura, the film stars Bradley Cooper, Leslie Bibb,
Brooke Shields, Roger Bart, Ted Raimi and Vinnie Jones.
Its script was adapted by Jeff Buhler, the producer was Tom Rosenberg of
Lakeshore Entertainment, and it was released on August 1, 2008.
The film received mixed reviews.
Producer Joe Daley, a long-time friend of Buhler's, brought the two writers together and helped develop the script, along with producers Anthony DiBlasi and Jorge Saralegui, for their and Clive
Barker's production company Midnight Picture Show, which was responsible for Book of Blood, the next film adaptation from the anthology of short stories that spawned The Midnight Meat Train.
The film explores themes of photographer, gore, butcher, vegetarian, stalking.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.